<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ozette Cytoverse</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ozette Cytoverse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Cytoverse Post</title>
      <link>/2019/12/20/First-Cytoverse-Post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/20/First-Cytoverse-Post/</guid>
      <description>  This is just testing out how the blog is working. Here’s some code and stuff
library(flowWorkspace) ## As part of improvements to flowWorkspace, some behavior of ## GatingSet objects has changed. For details, please read the section ## titled &amp;quot;The cytoframe and cytoset classes&amp;quot; in the package vignette: ## ## vignette(&amp;quot;flowWorkspace-Introduction&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;flowWorkspace&amp;quot;) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/install/</guid>
      <description>Installation // Pandoc 2.9 adds attributes on both header and div. We remove the former (to // be compatible with the behavior of Pandoc :first-child&#34;); var i, h, a; for (i = 0; i 0) h.removeAttribute(a[0].name); } });  /*! jQuery v1.11.3 | (c) 2005, 2015 jQuery Foundation, Inc. | jquery.org/license */ !function(a,b){&#34;object&#34;==typeof module&amp;&amp;&#34;object&#34;==typeof module.exports?module.exports=a.document?b(a,!0):function(a){if(!a.document)throw new Error(&#34;jQuery requires a window with a document&#34;);return b(a)}:b(a)}(&#34;undefined&#34;!=typeof window?window:this,function(a,b){var c=[],d=c.slice,e=c.concat,f=c.push,g=c.indexOf,h={},i=h.toString,j=h.hasOwnProperty,k={},l=&#34;1.11.3&#34;,m=function(a,b){return new m.fn.init(a,b)},n=/^[\s\uFEFF\xA0]+|[\s\uFEFF\xA0]+$/g,o=/^-ms-/,p=/-([\da-z])/gi,q=function(a,b){return b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citing the Cytoverse</title>
      <link>/citation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/citation/</guid>
      <description>If you find the Cytoverse software packages to be useful in your research leading to a publication, develop tools that depend on these packages, or reproduce code from these packages in your own software, please appropriately cite the paper corresponding to initial development of the corresponding package(s).
Citations are incorporated in to each of the packages, so these can be easily obtained from within R by (using flowWorkspace as an example):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help</title>
      <link>/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/help/</guid>
      <description>Bug Reports and Feature Requests The Cytoverse team greatly appreciates users bringing any unexpected behavior to our attention as well as requesting additional functionality or documentation that they would find helpful. For any of these purposes please open an issue on the GitHub page for the relevant package repository, all of which can be found from the RGLab GitHub homepage.
If you are reporting a bug, please try to generate a reproducible example (or &amp;ldquo;reprex&amp;rdquo;) for generating the unexpected behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Instructions</title>
      <link>/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/install/</guid>
      <description>Versions Both the latest stable releases of all Cytoverse packages and more up-to-date development builds can be installed from Bioconductor. If you have not already done so, you will need to install BiocManager by running the following in R:
if (!requireNamespace(&amp;quot;BiocManager&amp;quot;, quietly = TRUE)) install.packages(&amp;quot;BiocManager&amp;quot;) The most up-to-date development versions can also be built from sources available from Github. If you are building from source on Windows, you will need to install Rtools and will need to follow some additional instructions for installing RProtoBufLib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Cytoverse</title>
      <link>/learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started The Cytoverse team continually works to make the packages more approachable to new users, even as new tools are added. To that end, the best place to start is with the package vignettes. All of the Cytoverse packages have a number of vignettes intended to provide a brief introduction to the role they serve. After installation, these can be accessed from within R by running browseVignettes(&amp;quot;package_name&amp;quot;) where &amp;ldquo;package_name&amp;rdquo; would be &amp;ldquo;flowWorkspace&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;openCyto&amp;rdquo;, or whichever package you needed to learn about.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>